prospero.com 2015-09-07

# Mzinga Privacy - Mzinga

**Privacy Policy**

**WHO WE ARE AND WHAT THIS IS**

Mzinga provides on-demand social intelligence solutions and services in the learning, marketing, and customer experience markets.

We take the private nature of your personal information very seriously, and are committed to protecting it. To that end, we’ve set up procedures to ensure that your information is handled responsibly and in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws.

**“Personal information”** is any information that can be used to identify an individual. It does not include personal information that is encoded or anonymized, or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public information.

This privacy policy describes what information we collect when you visit Mzinga, how we use that information, and what choices we offer you to access, update, and control it. This version of the policy is effective as of May 10, 2013.

**SAFE HARBOR OVERVIEW**

Mzinga complies with the principles of the Safe Harbor Framework developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce in consultation with the European Commission and the Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner of Switzerland, except where limited by any legal, regulatory, ethical or public interest considerations. More information about the principles that make up the Framework, as well as other frequently asked questions relating to Safe Harbor can be found at: <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>.

In accordance with our commitment to protect personal privacy, Mzinga adheres to the principles of the Safe Harbor Framework as developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce in consultation with the European Commission. The seven principles and Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) referred to in this policy compose Safe Harbor privacy framework. These principles and FAQs may be found at: <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

We collect information two ways: Information we get from your use of a Mzinga product offering, and information you provide to us directly from the Mzinga Web Site.

**Information we get from your use of Mzinga’s product line** is primarily non-personally- identifying information of the sort that web browsers, servers, and third party services typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the time of each visit. Other non-identifying information that we might have access to includes how you use the Service (e.g. search queries), your approximate location, cookies, etc.

We collect this non-personally-identifying information in order to better understand how visitors use the Service and, where possible, to improve their experience. For instance, we log the time it takes to run database queries so that we can improve performance.

We also collect potentially personally identifying information in the form of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) accessed (which may reference the name of a board, card, or organization), and the unique identification number associated with the account. We don’t use that information to identify you, with one exception: we may discover, by reviewing log files, that a particular account is degrading the experience for all users. If this is discovered, we may look up personally identifiable information associated with that account in order to contact the account owner. We handle and disclose this information in the same way we handle other potentially personally identifying information as described below.

**Information Provided to Mzinga**

Mzinga may collect personal data from customers through a transaction or inquiry, your submission of a form, registrations, or communication to us.  Information may also be gathered from third-party sources (including without limitation, opt-in lists, publicly available data, consumer reporting agencies, other companies, and referrals) and through your activities and interactions with us.  We may combine data collected from these disparate sources unless we tell you otherwise.

The types of personal data typically collected by Mzinga may include the following, depending on your activities:

Contact information, including name, title, street address (home, work), postal code, country, telephone numbers (home, work, cell, etc.), email address (home, work), company name, and other similar information.

Personal/demographic information, e.g.  gender, or level of education.

Transactional information, including products or services you inquire about, or request.

User content, including information provided when you use one of our online communities, forums or other online means of communications, and all other user submissions and content you provide.

**INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO DISPLAY PUBLICLY**

Some users may elect to publicly post personally identifying or sensitive information about themselves in their normal use of our communities. This could occur through use of the optional profile fields, in interactions or on public discussion boards. Information like that, which is voluntarily posted in publicly visible areas, is considered to be public, even if it would otherwise be considered to be personally identifying or sensitive. As such, it is not subject to the protocols listed below, because we don’t control it; you do. Additionally, voluntarily publicizing such information means that you lose any privacy rights you might normally have with regards to that information. It may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications, like spam.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

  * To allow you to register and to administer and process the registration
  * To communicate with you about our products, services and related issues
  * To evaluate the quality of our products and services, and to enhance your experience on our web sites
  * To maintain and administer our web sites and comply with our legal or internal obligations and policies
  * To transfer information to others as described in this policy or to satisfy our legal, regulatory, compliance, or auditing requirements

We may disclose personal data you provide to our affiliates and partners and to consultants, service providers, and contractors that we use to support our business and operations (e.g., delivery services, financial institutions, fulfillment services, technical support, advertising, public relations, media and marketing services, legal services, call-in centers, e-commerce and other web-related services such as web hosting and web monitoring services, and event-related services such as online and offline data capture services) who have agreed to keep the information confidential and use it only to provide the applicable service(s).

We may also disclose personal data to third parties (including without limitation, governmental agencies) if required to do so by law, regulation, or court order; to respond to governmental and/or law enforcement requests; to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with our (or others’) rights or property; to support any claim, defense, or declaration in a case or before any jurisdictional and/or administrative authority, arbitration, or mediation panel; or in connection with disciplinary actions/investigations.

We may disclose and/or transfer Personal Information to a third party in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale.  We will try to notify you of any changed in ownership or sale by either posting it on our site or by emailing you (at the email address in the system).

If you are a registered user of Mzinga and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on. If we do send you information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with a way to request that you don’t get any similar notices (opt-out).

Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when you are first asked to provide us with personal information, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and we’ll notify you before we use the information for something other than the purpose for which it was originally collected. If anything in this policy seems unclear, please don’t hesitate to contact us at [privacy@mzinga.com](mailto:privacy@mzinga.com), so we can address your question and possibly clarify this document.

  **ONWARD TRANSFER**

Prior to providing agents with any personal information, we will obtain assurances that they will safeguard it in accordance with this policy. Examples of assurances that may be provided include:

  * A commitment that they will handle the information in accordance with this policy, or will provide the same level of protection, as required by the Safe Harbor Principles, subject to EU Directive 95/46/EC (“the EU Data Protection Directive”);
  * Safe Harbor certification by the agent, or being subject to another European Commission adequacy finding.

In the unlikely event that we should discover that an agent is using personal information in a way that conflicts with this policy, we will take all reasonable steps to stop them immediately.

**SECURITY**

 Mzinga takes appropriate steps to protect personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, or destruction, whether in transmission or storage.

All such electronic information is stored on restricted database servers. We only disclose such information to our employees, contractors or partners that a) need to know that information in order to process it for us or to provide other services, and b) have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Please keep in mind, however, there is no such thing as perfect security, and no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free.  Moreover, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any user name or password you use.

**COPPA REQUIREMENTS**

We do not intentionally gather personal information about visitors who are under 13 years of age.

**ACCESS**

Upon request, we will provide you with reasonable access to the personal information we collect about you. Because personal information—for example, your email address—is required to use our products, we retain personal information as long as your account is active. You will have the opportunity to correct, update, modify or delete this information updating your information in the systems of record. Please note that some information may remain in our records even after you request deletion of your information as permitted by the Safe Harbor Principles. Additionally, there may be limits to the amount of information we can practically provide. For example, we may limit an individual’s access to personal information where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the individual’s privacy or where doing so would violate others’ rights.

**ENFORCEMENT AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

 We will conduct internal audits of our compliance with this privacy policy, including an annual self-assessment.

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or about how you think Mzinga has handled your personal information, please contact [privacy@mzinga.com](mailto:privacy@mzinga.com).

Written Inquiries can be sent to:

Data Protection, Mzinga, Inc.   
10 Burlington Mall Road, Suite 111   
Burlington, MA 01803   
USA

If the complaint cannot be resolved through Mzinga’s internal processes, we will cooperate with JAMS, an arbitration and mediation service provider, under the JAMS International Mediation Rules.  These rules are accessible on the JAMS website at [www.jamsadr.com/rules-international-rules](http://www.jamsadr.com/rules-international-rules).

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will include a new effective date, and will be posted on this page.
